Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
- Pacific Telesis Group (Pacific Telephone), Publication (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Management Handbook, Publication (Box 24, Folder 16)
    By Pacific Telesis Group. January 1982. Item is in English.
- Packard Electric, Publication (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Packard Electric: Division of General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 24, Folder 17)
    By Packard Electric. Item is in English.
- Parker Pen Company, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Highlights of the Office Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    By Parker Pen Company. March 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    By Parker Pen Company. May 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    By Parker Pen Company. February 3, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Manager/ Supervisor Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    By Parker Pen Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Exempt Employee Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Equal Employment Opportunity Policy, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    By Parker Pen Company. August 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Corpoate Facts Book, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Equal Employment Opportunity Policy, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
    By Parker Pen Company. February 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Non-Exempt Employee Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Pay Equity Commission, Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Questions and Answers: Pay Equity in the Workplace, Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
    By Pay Equity Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Pay Equity Affects You, Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
- KPMG, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: World Magazine No. 1, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
    By KPMG. 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: World Magazine No. 2, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
    By KPMG. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: World Magazine Summer 1988, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
    By KPMG. Summer 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: World Magazine May-June 1986, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: World Magazine Sept-Oct. 1985, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: World Magazine Vol. 19 Number 1, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: World Magazine Vol. 18 No. 1, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: World Magazine Vol. 18 No. 4, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
- KPMG, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: World Magazine Vol 18 No. 2, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: World Magazine No. 3, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: World Magazine No. 3, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: World Magazine No. 4, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: World Magazine No. 4, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: World Magazine Vol. 20 No. 5, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: World Magazine Jan-Mar. 1987, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: World Magazine April-June 1987, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co. - House Organs, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: World Magazine July- September 1987, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co. July-September 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: World Magazine Winter 1988, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: World Magazine Spring 1988, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: World Magazine Fal 1987, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: World Magazine Spring 1989, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: World Magazine No. 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: World Magazine No. 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: World Magazine No. 3, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: World Magazine No. 1, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: World Magazine No. 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Penn Central Transportation Company - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Team Up with Penn Central: First in Transportation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    By Penn Central Transportation Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Penn Central Supplemental Pension Plan: for employees in non-agreement positions, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: College Recruitment Procedures Guide, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Pennsylvania State Univ. Dept. of Labor Studies, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Union Member's Guide to the New Right, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    By Paul F. Clark. Item is in English.
- Pension Benefit Guarantee Corp., Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Planning your Retirement: The Individual Retirement Account Option, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 31, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-Multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Letter from Peter A. Kirsch, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 15, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Those rates and quantities should continue in effect for plans terminating in October 1983, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 15, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Those Rates and quantities should continue in effect for plans terminating in November 1983, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 15, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Rates and Quantities should continue in effect for plans terminating in January 1984, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 15, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Letter from Peter A. Kirsch, Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. January 16, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Letter regarding Federal Register, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. February 22, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Letter from Peter A. Kirsch, Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 15, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Letter from Peter A. Kirsch, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. April 13, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Alternative Allocation Methods, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 19, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Waiver of Seller's Bond, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 1, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Letter from Peter A. Kirsch, Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. August 1, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Letter from Peter A. Kirsch, Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 1, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: PBGC Actuarial Tables Rates and Period, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: News! Vol. 9 No. 9, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Letter from Peter A. Kirsch, Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 15, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Letter from Peter A. Kirsch, Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. May 15, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Letter from Peter A. Kirsch, Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. April 15, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Letter from E. William Fitzgerald, Acting Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 14, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Acting Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 28, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Acting Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 15, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Acting Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 13, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Acting Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 30, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Acting Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 15, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Bulletin, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 10, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Acting Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 13, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 15, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Acting Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Acting Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. January 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Director, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. February 14, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: News: PBGC Issues Reminder on Accelerated Premium Payment Requirements, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. January 24, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Director Communications, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 31, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Director Communications, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 14, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Letter about Federal Register, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. May 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Letter about Federal Register, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. April 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Interest Rates for Valuing Multiemployer Plans Following Mass Withdrawal, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. April 30, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Letter from E. William FitzGerald, Director Communications, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 13, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Letter from Judith E. Bekelman, Director Communications, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 27, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Letter from Judith E. Bekelman, Director Communications, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Letter from Judith E. Bekelman, Director Communications, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. August 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 47: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 26, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 14, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 29, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. February 13, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 13, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 27, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Valluation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. April 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. May 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 26, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-Multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 60: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 30, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 62: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Valuation Interst Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 13, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-MultiEmployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 65: PBGC Announces Maximum Guarantee for 1988, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 23, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 67: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 68: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-Multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 70: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 30, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 72: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. January 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 74: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. May 13, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. April 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 77: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 78: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 79: PBGC Issues Interim Rule on Paument of Pension Insurance Premiums, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 30, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 80: Interest Rate for Determination of Variable Rate Premium Amount, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 81: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 82: PBGC Issues Interim Rule on Payment of Pension Insurance Premiums, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 83: Interest Rate for Determination of Variable Rate Premium Amount, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 84: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 85: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 86: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 87: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 88: Interest Rate for Determination of Variable Rate Premium Amount, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. August 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 89: Interest Rate for Determination of Variable Rate Premium Amount, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 90: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 30, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 91: Interest Rates for Valuing Vested Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 92: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 5, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 93: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 94: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 14, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 95: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 96: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 28, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 97: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 98: Interest Rates for Valuing VestedBenefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 99: Interest Rates for Valuing Vested Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 100: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. January 6, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 101: Interest Rates for Valuing Vested Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. February 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 102: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 103: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 31, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 104: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 105: Interest Rates for Valuing Vested Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. May 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 106: Interest Rates for Valuing Vsted Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 107: Letter from Judith E. Bekelman, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 108: Letter from Judith E. Bekelman, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 14, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 109: Letter from Judith E. Bekelman, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 110: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 30, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 111: 1989 Annual Premium Payment Package Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 10, 1989. Item is in English.
- Pepsi-Cola Company, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Pepsi-Cola Company and the MBA, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
    By Pepsi-Cola Company. Item is in English.
- Peterson Builders, Inc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employees Manual, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By Peterson Builders, Inc. June 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Safety Manual, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By Peterson Builders, Inc. May 1981. Item is in English.
- Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Pfizer Today: Bringing Science to Life, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    By Pfizer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Imagine Yourself at Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Pfizer Scene, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    By Pfizer. December 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: December 11, 1980, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    By PfizerPfizer Pulse Vol. 11 No. 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Report on Equal Opportunity Affairs, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Welcome: A Handbook for Pfizer Headquarters Employees, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Pfizer: A World of Choice, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Educational Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Summary of Pfizer Policies on Business Conduct, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: MBA Opportunities at Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Pfizer Inc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Top Opportunity Bulletin, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    By Pfizer. Februray 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Imagine Yourself at Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Pfizer in Action: A Report on Corporate Responsibility, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Pharmaceutical Executive: A Business and Marketing Publication, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Employee Benefits Highlights, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Annual Report to Employees, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Welcome to the World of Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)